They aim to misbehave.
Serenity is a science fiction, action, adventure film directed by Joss Whedon.
When the renegade crew of Serenity agrees to hide a fugitive on their ship, they find themselves in an action-packed battle between the relentless military might of a
totalitarian regime who will destroy anything – or anyone – to get the girl back and the bloodthirsty creatures who roam the uncharted areas of space.
the greatest danger of all may be on their ship.
Malcolm 'Mal' Reynolds, played by Nathan Fillion.
River Tam, played by Summer Glau.
Zoë Alleyne Washburne, played by Gina Torres.
Hoban 'Wash' Washburne, played by Alan Tudyk.
Inara Serra, played by Morena Baccarin.
Jayne Cobb, played by Adam Baldwin.
Serenity is a 2005 American space Western film written and directed
by Joss Whedon in his feature directorial debut.
The film is a continuation of Whedon's short-lived 2002 Fox television series Firefly, taking place after the events of the final episode, with all of the main
cast reprising their roles, including Nathan Fillion, Alan Tudyk, Adam Baldwin, and Summer Glau, while Chiwetel Ejiofor stars as a new character.
Set in 2517, the story follows the crew of Serenity, a "Firefly-class" spaceship, whose captain and first mate are
veterans of the Unification War, having fought on the losing Independent side against the Alliance.
Their lives of smuggling and cargo-running are interrupted by a
psychic passenger who harbors a dangerous secret.
Serenity was released in North America on September 30, 2005, by Universal Pictures to generally positive reviews and several accolades, including the Hugo
Award for Best Dramatic Presentation, the Prometheus Special Award and the Nebula Award for Best Script, but underperformed at the box office.
The film explores themes of spacecraft, martial
arts, telepathy, dystopia, fugitive.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.